<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Mooshak</title><link>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Mooshak</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Linux Client</title><link>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/clients/linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/clients/linux/</guid><description>Mooshak Linux Client # Mooshak Linux Client uses sshuttle internally and it just handles what arguments are passed to sshuttle if ran with or without websocket tunnel.
Requirements # To use Mooshak linux client, you will need to install python interpreter installed on your system(tested on 3.8, but 3.6+ is enough).
Installation # First, clone the repository or download it as a zip and move it into directory of your choice.</description></item><item><title>Server</title><link>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/server/</guid><description>Mooshak Server # Setup # To setup a mooshak server you will need git, docker and docker compose (comes with docker itself in latest versions) installed.
Go to directory of your choice and clone the project.
git clone https://github.com/sepgh/mooshak Next, go to newly cloned mooshak directory and then navigate to server directory.
cd mooshak # cloned directory cd server # server scripts After that, create required docker volume and networks, then you can start mooshak by runing the docker compose:</description></item><item><title>Windows Client</title><link>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/clients/windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sepgh.github.io/mooshak/docs/clients/windows/</guid><description>Mooshak Windows Client # This page describess how to run Mooshak Windows Client.
This client is written in python for easier development in future. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to install python you can try pre-built version from releases or poormans vpn batch script.
Update: tunnel all of your windows machine traffic using virtual machine # The Linux Client of mooshak depends on SSHuttle directly. The article below explains how to use Oracle Virtual Box to run SSHuttle inside linux VM in a windows host and proxy all your traffic through it.</description></item></channel></rss>